-How's Dev?  -I I managed to get him in a med bay He's recovering
-德福怎么样  -我想办法让他进医院了 他正在康复
-Itching to get back in the fight.  -Good.
-渴望回到战斗中来  -很好
We're going to need him. And a whole lot more just like him.
我们会需要他的 还需要很多像他一样的人
Seg..I know losing Ona was hard for Kem,.
赛格 我知道对凯姆来说失去欧娜很难受
but sending him to Kryptonopolis...Was that to help him or to help you?
但是送他去氪星大都市 有帮到他或者是帮到你吗
I'm worried you're starting to think this fight we're in, that maybe we can't win it.
我担心你开始觉得 我们所参与的战斗  也许是赢不了的
Is that what you think?
你是这么想的吗
Everything that Adam said...about my grandson, about the Els, about who we are...
亚当说的那些 关于我孙子的  关于艾尔家族的 关于我是谁的
who we're meant to be. He believed that I could save the universe.
我们应该是谁的那些 他相信我能拯救这个宇宙
I couldn't even save him.
我甚至都救不了他
I've lost too many people already, Lyta. I can't lose anyone else.
莉塔  我已经失去了太多人了 我不能再失去他们了